<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Simon Perche</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Simon Perche</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>fr-fr</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://simonperche.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Atlassian Deployment Triggers</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/contributions/deploy-triggers/</guid><description>Addressed pretty significant page load performance issue founde in larger deployments. Eliminates uses of intensive backend query, replacing it with an asynchronous API call against a lucene index. This change reduces page load from from 2+ minutes to nearly instant, with an incredibly responsive UI.</description></item><item><title>Data-Augmentation for Deep Learning Based Remote Photoplethysmography Methods</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/publications/darppg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/publications/darppg/</guid><description>Simon Perche, Deivid Botina, Yannick Benezeth, Keisuke Nakamura, Randy Gomez, Johel Miteran
Abstract Acquisition of remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) signals using deep learning-based methods has become very important for the measurement of heart rate (HR). These methods are known to require a large amount of data during training, so data augmentation is often used. In this paper we propose a methodology for data augmentation to be used as a pre-training step. We tested our proposed method using transfer-learning in three public databases, and we demonstrate that it helps the neural network to learn the main features of the videos.</description></item><item><title>An assessment of algorithms to estimate respiratory rate from the remote photoplethysmogram</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/publications/assessmentrppg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/publications/assessmentrppg/</guid><description>Duncan Luguern, Simon Perche, Yannick Benezeth, Virginie Moser, L Andrea Dunbar, Fabian Braun, Alia Lemkaddem, Keisuke Nakamura, Randy Gomez, Julien Dubois
Abstract The respiratory rate is important information in the healthcare environment. Consequently, research is done to develop a device that could measure the respiratory rate continuously with non-contact devices. Various methods were tried, such as radio-based, thermal imaging or remote photoplethysmography (rPPG).
The rPPG method uses a video recording of the skin in ambient light conditions.</description></item><item><title>Added Docker Build Status Badge to shields.io</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/contributions/shields-docker/</guid><description>Shields.io is a massive library of badges that can be inserted into project README&amp;rsquo;s or websites displaying various statuses (code coverage, health, version, etc). Support for docker was missing the current build health, and was a pretty trivial addition.</description></item><item><title>Schema.org Structured Data documentation fixes</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/contributions/schema-org/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:08:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/contributions/schema-org/</guid><description>While adding Structured Data to a client&amp;rsquo;s website I found some example JSON that was invalid. Simple contribution to cleanup the user documentation providing syntactically valid JSON documents.</description></item><item><title>BOSH release for Bamboo &amp; Remote Agents</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/creations/bosh-agents/</guid><description>BOSH (Bosh Outer SHell) &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip; is an open source tool for release engineering, deployment, lifecycle management, and monitoring of distributed systems.&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s amazingly powerful. This examples uses BOSH to provision an Alassian vendor app running on JDK along with the support Postgres database and agents to support it. The releases manages the health of services and will automatically provision, start/stop processes across the various services.</description></item><item><title>Forcing Visits to use SSL</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</guid><description>Intro Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter whether it&amp;rsquo;s a CakePHP app for a client, your own personal CMS, or any other web based application. If your passing around passwords or other sensitive info you should really implement SSL. SSL provides 2 main perks to your visitors.
First it encrypts all communication that flies across the web. This prevents curious or devious billies from getting your secrets. Secondly it ensures to the user that your server is in fact who it claims, and not a nasty &amp;lsquo;man in the middle&amp;quot; attack.</description></item><item><title>Atlassian Marketplace Plugins</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/creations/marketplace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/creations/marketplace/</guid><description>Multiple plugins used by thousands of teams that provide enhanced functionality of Atlassian’s core products (primarily JIRA and Bamboo) to enrich CI/CD capabilities, DevOps automation, or productivity. Functionality spans user interface, web services and persistence.</description></item><item><title>Docker image for Bitbucket CI/CD Pipelines  "shipit"</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/projects/creations/docker-marketplace/</guid><description>Provides required dependencies and additional utilities to simplify and codify the process of building, testing and delivering Atlassian plugins all the way to the live marketplace. Executes integration/AUT level tests against all stated compatible versions for the productUploads generated artifact to Atlassian marketplaceProvides corresponding metadata indicating version, release notes, and compatibility</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description></item></channel></rss>