<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Heart rate on Simon Perche</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/tags/heart-rate/</link><description>Recent content in Heart rate on Simon Perche</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>fr-fr</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://simonperche.github.io/tags/heart-rate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data-Augmentation for Deep Learning Based Remote Photoplethysmography Methods</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/publications/darppg/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/publications/darppg/</guid><description>Simon Perche, Deivid Botina, Yannick Benezeth, Keisuke Nakamura, Randy Gomez, Johel Miteran
Abstract Acquisition of remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) signals using deep learning-based methods has become very important for the measurement of heart rate (HR). These methods are known to require a large amount of data during training, so data augmentation is often used. In this paper we propose a methodology for data augmentation to be used as a pre-training step. We tested our proposed method using transfer-learning in three public databases, and we demonstrate that it helps the neural network to learn the main features of the videos.</description></item><item><title>An assessment of algorithms to estimate respiratory rate from the remote photoplethysmogram</title><link>https://simonperche.github.io/publications/assessmentrppg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://simonperche.github.io/publications/assessmentrppg/</guid><description>Duncan Luguern, Simon Perche, Yannick Benezeth, Virginie Moser, L Andrea Dunbar, Fabian Braun, Alia Lemkaddem, Keisuke Nakamura, Randy Gomez, Julien Dubois
Abstract The respiratory rate is important information in the healthcare environment. Consequently, research is done to develop a device that could measure the respiratory rate continuously with non-contact devices. Various methods were tried, such as radio-based, thermal imaging or remote photoplethysmography (rPPG).
The rPPG method uses a video recording of the skin in ambient light conditions.</description></item></channel></rss>